They exist.
Mermaid Down is a horror, fantasy, mystery film directed by Jeffrey Grellman.
A mermaid is ripped from the ocean by a fishing crew only to
be tortured and to have her tail cut off.
A seemingly helpful stranger intervenes, but then locks her away in an institution for
mentally disturbed young women, where no one believes she is a mermaid.
With no way out, she is forced to count on her survival
instincts, and fight for her life at all costs.
The Mermaid, played by Alexandra Bokova.
Ghost, played by Meggan Kaiser.
Dr. Beyer, played by Burt Culver.
Sandra, played by Michelle Gallagher.
Stanley, played by Shepherd Stevenson.
Dr. Miller, played by Phillip Andre Botello.
The Little Mermaid is a 2023 American musical fantasy film that is a live-action adaptation of Disney's 1989 animated film The Little Mermaid, which itself
is loosely based on Hans Christian Andersen's 1837 fairy tale, produced by Walt Disney Pictures, DeLuca Marshall, and Marc Platt Productions.
Directed by Rob Marshall from a screenplay by David Magee, the film stars Halle Bailey as the title character, with Jonah Hauer-King,
Daveed Diggs, Awkwafina, Jacob Tremblay, Noma Dumezweni, Art Malik, Javier Bardem, and Melissa McCarthy in supporting roles.
The plot follows the mermaid princess Ariel, who is fascinated with the human world; after saving
Prince Eric from a shipwreck, she makes a deal with the sea witch Ursula to walk on land.
Plans for a remake of 1989's The Little Mermaid were confirmed in May 2016.
In December 2017, Disney announced Marshall was
being courted to direct the film.
Bailey, Hauer-King, McCarthy, Bardem, Diggs, Tremblay, Awkwafina, and the
rest of the cast joined between July and November 2019.
Production was expected to begin in London between late March and early April 2020 but was delayed by the COVID-19 pandemic, before
ultimately took place from January to July 2021, primarily at Pinewood Studios in England and on the island of Sardinia, Italy.
Composer Alan Menken returned to augment the score and write new songs alongside Lin-Manuel
Miranda, who serves as a producer with Platt, John DeLuca, and Marshall.
The film is dedicated to the late Howard Ashman, who co-produced
and co-wrote the songs from the original film.
The Little Mermaid premiered at the Dolby Theatre in Los Angeles on May 8, 2023, and was
released in the United States on May 26 by Walt Disney Studios Motion Pictures.
The film received mixed reviews from critics and has grossed $569.6 million worldwide against its
production budget of $240.2 million, becoming Disney's twenty-third most expensive to date.
The film explores themes of asylum, mermaid, mental, alexandrabokova.
The tone is intense and dark and mind_bending.